## CHRISTOPHER HAGE

6/20 RIDDELL ROAD, HOLDEN HILL 5088; 0422638193; CHAGES16@GMAIL.COM; D.O.B: 16/10/1985

### **OBJECTIVE**

My goal is to utilise the leadership and customer service skills I have gained as a Frontline Manager and Sales Person over the last 11 years at TPG to the best of my ability. I have worked sales and customer service within the telecommunication industry, and am now looking for a new, challenging role with a new company. My goal is to find a suitable career with a respectable employer where I can continue to refine my sales and customer service skills.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2019 UNITI WIRELESS Adelaide, SA

#### **CUSTOMER SERVICE OFFICE**

- Technical Support For Wireless and Fixed Line Services
- Billing Enquiries
- · Cancellation and Retention Enquiries
- Responding to Emails

# 14/11/2016 TO 16/02/2019 TPG BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT MANAGER

- Competitive Sales environment- Corporate Grade IP Services
- Identify Solutions that would assist in improving Business day to day efficiency
- Retention
- Corporate Account Management- Billing, Support, Service Delivery
- Face to Face client meetings
- Training and coaching of new staff
- Assistance in migration to new infrastructure and services
- Worked closely with Channel Partner team and resellers to assist clients

## 17/5/2013 TO 14/11/2016 iiNet Adelaide, SA

## **BUSINESS SALES CUSTOMER SERVICE MANAGER**

- Training, mentoring and coaching CSRs
- Introducing team members to Adherence, ACW
- Implementing NPS for the team-Exceeding targets over the last 4 months and winning an internal NPS competition within the BCC.
- Performance Management
- Efficiently handling escalations and TIO complaints
- Implementation of NPS and Conversion Rate competitions for the Business team
- Exceeded all Adherence, NPS and Conversion rate targets for the H1 2014
- Increased Team NPS from 30% to 70%
- Promoting company and NBN at Victor Harbor Business Conference

#### 29/6/2009 TO 17/5/2013 Internode/ iiNet Adelaide, SA

## **BUSINESS SALES TEAM LEADER**

- Reporting to the National Sales Manager
- Implemented Outbound Sales Campaigns
- Assisted with the introduction of a commission-based incentive plan within the department
- Created and altered processes, including the Relocation process in order to improve efficiency

Adelaide, SA

- Training, mentoring and coaching staff.
- Ran Business Sales product trainings for CSRs in other departments
- Generated reporting systems using Excel in order to save time collating data for the team
- Maintained Rosters for the team without the support of the WFM department.

19/6/2007 TO 26/6/2009

Internode

Adelaide, SA

#### SALES REPRESENTATIVE

- Selling ADSL, VOIP, DNS, Webhosting to Business and Residential customers
- Sales Person of The Quarter Residential Sales July-September 2007
- Sales Person of The Quarter Residential Sales October-December 2007

.

2002 TO 2006

McDonald's

Felixstow, SA

### **CREW TRAINER**

- Training and mentoring new staff
- Food Preparation
- Stock Rotation
- Counting Money

## **EDUCATION**

## 2011

CERTIFICATE IV FRONTLINE MANAGEMENT

2004-2007
BACHELOR OF MEDIA

University of Adelaide

Adelaide, SA

## **REFERENCES**

Bill Elsayed- 0447 348 880

Further TPG, iiNet and Internode References are available on request.